gg.deals 2019-12-31

# Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy was updated on May 23, 2018.

Your privacy is important to us so we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your personal information.

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and contact us if you have any questions.

### **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with us. We may share this personal information certain third-party service providers and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our services or respond to any queries you may have.

Here are some examples of the types of personal information we may collect and how we may use it:

### **What personal information we collect**

When you are creating an account we may collect a variety of information, including your mailing address, email address, contact preferences, device identifiers, IP address and location information. Some of our services also require your Steam login information acquired via official Steam API.

### **How we use your personal information**

We may process your personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy with your consent, for compliance with a legal obligation or when we have assessed it is necessary to maintain our services.

We use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our services, content and advertising. We may also use your personal information for account and network security purposes, including in order to protect our services for the benefit of all our users

We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services.

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with our website, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our services, and customer communications.

If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

### **Cookies and Other Technologies**

Our websites, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use "cookies". These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non‑personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

If you want to disable cookies, check with your internet browser provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most internet services, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit websites and applications, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, to improve our product and services, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

### **Service Providers**

We shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, or advertising on our website. These companies are obligated to protect your information - the full list of these companies as well as information that they use can be found at the end of this Policy.

### **Others**

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for us  to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our users.

### **Protection of Personal Information**

All information that we gather is stored on a secure server in an encrypted form. In case of a security breach, as outlined in the GDPR regulations, we intend to inform authorities within 72 hours of the nature and extent of the breach, and, in case sensitive data was compromised, to contact all affected users with information on what data was compromised.

### **Integrity and Retention of Personal Information**

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy and our service specific privacy summaries.When assessing these periods we carefully examine our need to collect personal information at all and if we establish a relevant need we only retain it for the shortest possible period to realize the purpose of collection unless a longer retention period is required by law.

### **Access to Personal Information**

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by updating your account page. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with access (including a copy) for any purpose including to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if we are not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes.We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. We may also decline aspects of deletion or access requests if we believe doing so would undermine our legitimate use of data for anti-fraud and security purposes as described earlier.

### **Privacy Questions**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or data processing, you would like to contact us via our contact form.

We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

### **List of third-party service providers, and data that is being shared**

DigitalOcean ([GDPR](https://gg.deals/redirect/92202a236e283240d6eb3b2c81d9fbafc369e569/)) - website hosting service, maintains all data on the servers.

Google Analytics ([GDPR](https://gg.deals/redirect/5e70c8780044fd299e48b0f322503328b6fbd42c/)) - IP, browser and location data, website navigation history.

Hotjar ([GDPR](https://gg.deals/redirect/8cca3bb19abf2deb2519d9dca509db7bb4140fa3/)) - records all user activity. It creates recordings of how user navigates through the website and generates heatmaps of clicks on our website. It also enables us to send polls to users

Disqus ([GDPR](https://gg.deals/redirect/a1c1255cccd41e576e15d58928df2389ce77d768/)) - email address, IP.

Gleam ([GPDR](https://gleam.io/privacy)) – name, social network profiles, IP, email address.

Referral services - website navigation history for billing purposes.
